Dishant Man Sthapit

A: Auburn, Sydney 2144 T: 0410 330 140

E: dishantsthapit@gmail.com

L: www.linkedin.com/in/dishantsthapit

Career Objective

I am working as a developer with a Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology from Western Sydney University with local and professional experience looking forward to establish my future career. As a detail oriented person, with fast learning and communication skills, I can carry out a wide variety of development tasks with of multiple software responsibly and accurately.

Technical Skills

Programming Languages: HTML5, JavaScript (React), CSS, ASP.Net, ASP Classic

Computer Systems: Windows XP/Vista/7, Linux/Ubuntu, Mac

Web Servers: Windows Server 2008 and 2012

Computer Software: Eclipse, Git, SQL Server, Visual Studio Code, Basecamp, Freshdesk,

Sublime Text, MS Project, Trello, Slack

Testing: Unit Testing, browser testing, device testing, system testing, system integration

testing, technical testing

Education

Professional Year - Sep 2017 - July 2017

Performance Education, Sydney

Key Subjects: Australian Business Culture and Environment, Achieving Career Success, Professional Workplace Meeting and Writing, 12 weeks Internship Program

Bachelor of ICT - Jul 2015 - Jul 2017

Western Sydney University, Sydney

Key Subjects: Programming Technique, Programming Fundamentals and Database Design and

Development, Technologies of Web Applications

Key achievements: Deans Merit List 2015, 2016 and 2017, Member of Golden Key Honor Society

Diploma in Information Technology - Apr 2014 - Jun 2015

Sydney TAFE, Ultimo

Key subject: CISCO Networking

Projects

Interactive Vehicle Website - Nov 2018 - Jan 2019

iMotor, North Sydney

Objective: To develop a device responsive Hyundai dealer website with its reusable designing,

which consists of designing an SQL database, setting up CMS, developing asp,

HTML5 and javascript.

Tools:Sublime Text (HTML, CSS3, JS, ASP Classic)

Duties: To develop device responsive automotive website according to the design mentioned

by the client.

Result: Achieved good feedback from the client.

Employment History

Junior Web Developer - April 2018 - Present

iMotor, North Sydney

Responsibilities:

- Demonstrating strong use of front-end tool and develop website.
- Writing npm scripts using different packages to produce desired output
- Ability to debug the error across 1000+ websites hosted by the company
- Demonstrating an ability to learn new tasks when being taught by senior mentor and colleagues

Manager - May 2014 - April 2018

Hungry Jacks, Burwood

Responsibilities:

- Displaying strong verbal communication skills when dealing with 1200+ customers per day
- Demonstrating an ability to learn new tasks when being taught by senior managers to set rosters
- Proven problem-solving ability when resolving general technical issues regarding registers and customer complaints

Achievements: Selected as the Manager of the Month for June 2017, Promoted from Assistant Manager to Manager within 3 months of employment.

Personal Attributes

- Strong Time Management and Organisational
 - Developed through 3 years of successfully combining work and university studies.
 - Preparing and running a well-maintained shift during work.

Problem Solving

- Ability to make informed decisions
- Capability to take ownership in providing solutions to customers while working in the retail sector

Strong Learning Ability

- Demonstrated a high aptitude for learning new skills and handling technical difficulties in an efficient and prompt manner through utilising analytical skills and critical thinking
- Always ready to learn new stuffs at work and during university.

References

Can be provided upon request